>> 凯尔: 因为所有语言都具有类型转换，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Because all languages
have type conversions,
这意味着所有语言都有角式案例，包括 JavaScript。
that means all languages have
corner cases, including JavaScript.
人们喜欢用 JavaScript 的角落
It is interesting that people
like to use JavaScript's corner
对整个语文的弹药。
cases as ammunition against
the language as a whole.
把眼罩戴上
Just putting blinders on and
假装其他语言没有那些角落
pretending that other languages
don't have those corner cases and
我们不能制作 C++ 的视频，比如说我们肯定能，对吧 ?
we can't make work videos about C++, for
example, cuz we definitely can, right?
设计一个没有角箱的系统是不可能的。
It is impossible to design a system
that won't have corner cases.
JavaScript 有一些角例。
JavaScript has some corner cases.
与其制作有关视频的视频，我们应该了解这些角落案例和
Rather than making wap videos about them,
we should learn those corner cases and
了解如何有效管理和处理这些问题。
learn how to effectively manage and
work around them.
>> 演讲者 2: 他们比其他语言有更多的边角案例吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Do they have more
corner cases than other languages?
>> 凯尔: 这是一个有趣的问题，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle: That's an interesting question,
but
不是我想任何人能有效回答的问题
not one that I think anybody
could effectively answer.
因为什么是更重要的，我们才会喜欢上一个账户。
Because what is even more mean, and
we're just gonna like keep up account.
你怎么知道这个是不同的夸克还是
How can you tell whether this is
the distinct different quark or
就能从不同角度的角度来区分
the same corner case
from a different angle?
我不确定你是否真的能那样做
I'm not sure that you could
really do that sort of account.
更重要的问题是
And to the larger point of your question,
我唯一能理解的语言是 JavaScript
the only language that I even remotely
have understanding of is JavaScript.
所以我不能告诉你它是不是比 Python更有角。
So I can't tell you whether it's more or
less corner casey than Python.
但我知道， JavaScript 有角落，我知道你可以在他们身边工作。
But I know JavaScript has corner cases,
and I know you can work around them.
以下是其中一些角例的示例。
Here's an example of some
of these corner cases.
正如我所说，其中很多都与数字有关。
A lot of them have to do with numbers,
as I said.
这里有很多空弦记得那个
Here we've got number of empty string,
remember that one,
那是所有邪恶的根源
that's the root of all evil.
我们一会儿再谈这事
We'll talk about that more in a second.
诺尔斯和未定义的人有一些奇怪的地方
Knowles and
undefined have some weird corner cases.
本质上很多谬误都变成了数字
Essentially a lot of the falsy
values becoming numbers,
那里有很多角落的例子
those there were a lot
of the corner cases ar.
如果我们不做空的
We could have eliminated most of
those if we just not made empty
字符串变为零。
string becomes zero.
大部分都消失了
Most of these would go away.
>> 凯尔: 下面有一个有趣的例子，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Down at the bottom
there is an interesting example,
几乎没人会这样做
almost nobody ever does this.
但是如果您构造布尔对象的实例并提供
But if you construct an instance of
the boolean object and you give it
原始值为 false，将像 truthy 一样行事，因为
the primitive value false, it is going
to behave as if it is truthy, because
我们不做两个原始的事，我们只是问它是否在虚无的名单上 ?
we don't do a two primitive on it, we
just ask is it on the falsy list or not?
所以它是一个谬误的对象，对吧 ?
So it is a falsy object, right?
>> 凯尔: 但另一个例子说明了为什么您不应该使用这些
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yet another illustration of why
you should never use those particular
" 努基 " 一词的基本要素
fundamentals with the Nuki word.
>> 凯尔: 好的，我们来谈谈所有胁迫邪恶的根源，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: All right, let's talk about
that root of all coercion evil,
确保我们在这里绝对安全
just to make sure we're
absolutely clear here.
空字符串不仅变为零，而且
Not only does the empty
string become zero, but
任何满白空间的字符串也会变为零。
any string that's full of
white space also becomes zero.
因为两个号码操作都是第一条
Because the two number operations
first strips off all leading and
在进行强制之前跟踪空格。
trailing whitespace before
doing its coercion.
所有白色太空串的例子
So all examples of white
space strings of all forms,
最终还是会产生同样的零
still all end up producing that same zero.
>> 凯尔: 字面上，如果我能时间旅行并解决任何关于 JavaScript的事情，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Literally, if I could time travel
and fix any one thing about JavaScript,
这就是我要解决的问题
this is the thing I'd fix.
我要回去告诉布伦东，不，不，这主意糟透了
I'd go back and tell Brendon, no,
no, no, that's a terrible idea.
不要使空字符串变为零，使其成为名称。
Don't make empty string become zero,
make it become name.
所有这些问题都将自行解决。
All these other problems
would fix themselves.
顺便说下还有没有那么明显的角落
By the way, there are corner
cases that are not as obvious,
因为我们不是在对付典型的行动
because we're not dealing
with our typical operations.
记得我说过我认为数字化或数字化
So, remember I said that I thought that
the numberification or numerification or
不管这个词是什么我会在某种程度上决定
whatever that word is,
I'll decide on some word at some point.
但不管这个词是什么，要对我说的一个布尔值进行编号，
But whatever that word is, to numbering
a boolean I said to you, 1s and
0s 是个坏主意
0s are a bad idea.
可能，你们所有人都说，不，他们是个好主意。
And probably, all of you said,
no, they're a great idea.
这里有一个这样的例子。
Well, here's one such example.
1 小于 2，我们都以数学方式了解情况，因此
1 less than 2, we all know mathematically
that that is the case, and so
它让我们觉得 JavaScript 是真实的
it makes sense that
JavaScript gives us a true.
2 小于 3 也是 true。
2 less than 3 is also true.
但是我们尝试了 1 比 2 小于 3 ，然后我们得到了真实的，
But then we try 1 less than 2 less than 3,
and we get true, and
我们认为 JavaScript 是聪明的，做的正是正确的事情。
we think well JavaScript is just smart and
doing exactly the right thing.
并不是，因为实际发生的是一场意外。
Not exactly, because what's actually
happening there is an accident.
实际发生的情况是 1 小于 2 的人先进行评估，
What's actually happening is that 1
less than 2 gets evaluated first,
这将被求值为真正的第 9 行
which gets evaluated to true line 9.
那是因为你有一个非数字用的数字
And then because you have a non-numeric
being used with the less than operator,
它会把它变成一个数字
it's gonna try to turn it into a number.
所以要把它变成一号
So it's gonna turn it into the number 1,
and
你无意中把那个 1 比 3 不到，那就是真正的工作的原因。
you accidentally get that 1 is less than
3, that's the reason why true works.
而事故也不是建立你的计划的良好基础。
And accidents are not a good foundation
upon which to build your programs.
库兹让我们来看下一个例子。
Cuz let's watch what happens
in the next example.
我们尝试 3 大于 2 ， 2 大于 1 ，但操作，
We try the 3 greater than 2, and
the 2 greater than 1, but oops,
3 大于 2 大于 1，但失败。
3 greater than 2 greater than 1,
that fails.
因为 3 大于 2 为 true。
Because 3 greater than 2 is true.
大于 1 的 True 大于 1，为 false。
True greater than 1 is 1 greater than 1,
which is false.
> > 凯尔: 所以我觉得这是个糟糕的想法
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So
I think it's a terrible idea for
有胆量的胆量强迫自己去做数字
booleans to implicitly coerce
themselves to numbers.
从 1970 年开始的任何编程方式都依赖于能力
And any programming style from 1970
onward, that has relied upon the ability
我想是为了拿一个布尔值减去或加减
to take something that's boolean and
subtract or add it or something, I think,
一直在利用这个黑客但基本上是在做更糟的代码
has been taking advantage of that hack,
but basically making worse of code.
如果我能治好东西我就能把他的名字命名为优秀的名字
I would make the number coercion of
brilliant be name if I could fix things.